<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on igeaman</title>
    <link>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on igeaman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.146.7</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:19:57 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://igeaman.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Read Books Fast With Ai</title>
      <link>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/how-to-read-books-fast-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 08:19:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/how-to-read-books-fast-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s never been about how much you know. It’s always been about knowing how much you don’t know. You can only cook with the ingredients you have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your identity is reflected in your daily choices, and if you observe most people, they aren’t trying to do anything by their own desire. They may search for new information, but it’s not to make changes in their life, it’s to feel as if they are making progress by hoarding information to sound smart or look different without actually doing anything different.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You don’t read to find information than can already be found. You read to explore the unknown and pursue your curiosity. You read to discover things you didn’t know before and didn’t even think about searching with google and chatGPT. You read to expand your mind to places you didn’t know were there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You read to slowly reprogram who you are by exposing yourself to new ideas that can’t be intentionally searched by an identity that didn’t even think to search for them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your Mind doesn’t change with a few key points from a book summary or an AI generated summary. It changes when new ideas (actionable or not) that fill in missing pieces, challenges old beliefs, or give you a new angle to view a situation from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Obsession over actionable steps and bullet points summaries is just another manifestation of cheap dopamine and distraction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Purpose of Knowledge is action, not knowledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;consumption&#34;&gt;Consumption&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smart People Read in 2 layers&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Psychology</title>
      <link>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/social-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 13:14:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/social-psychology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Social Psycholgy is study of How Humans behave the way the behave. what influencer peoples behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is my first Blog</title>
      <link>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:04:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://igeaman.github.io/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here I will share learnings about psychology, business, coading, and other stuff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
